Finding Aid for Stellanova Osborn papers, 1907-1988
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Card Indices for biographical writings, 1 boxes
  - Biographical name index cards (Box 38)
Kee, John.
May 8, 1950, May 17, 1950
Kefauver, Estes, 1903-1963.
September 9, 1949, July 26, 1950, August 8, 1950, August 28, 1950, August 14, 1950, September 25, 1950, October 6, 1950, April 12, 1951, May 2, 1951, May 30, 1951, August 6, 1951, September 22, 1951, July 1, 1953, May 6, 1955, November 1, 1955
April 13, 1956, April 25, 1956, May 7, 1956, June 13, 1956, July 16, 1958, March 17, 1959, July 2, 1960, October 22, 1960, November 29, 1960, January 12, 1961, January 23, 1962, May 9, 1963, June 13, 1963
Kefauver, Nancy Patterson.
August 20, 1963, May 13, 1964
Kelsey, William Kline, 1885-
November 8, 1945, November 30, 1945, December 7, 1945, June 25, 1947, July 20, 1947, August 25, 1947, September 3, 1947, July 11, 1949, July 26, 1949, August 14, 1949, August 28, 1949, September 27, 1949, September 14, 1949, 1950
July 23, 1951, August 31, 1951, August 12, 1951, September 20, 1951, October 6, 1951, 1952, 1953, June 2, 1954, July 13, 1954, August 1954, 1955, 1956, July 22, 1957
July 30, 1957, August 15, 1957, September 11, 1957, August 28, 1957, December 26, 1957, 1958, 1959, 1960, 1961, 1962, 1963, January 11, 1964, February 24, 1964, May 30, 1964, June 21, 1964, August 27, 1964, 1965, 1966
Kessenich, Michiels van, baron.
1959, 1960, 1961, February 6, 1962, February 12, 1962, April 29, 1963, November 12, 1963, December 16, 1963, 1964, May 3, 1965, November 18, 1965, March 1, 1966, March 31, 1966, August 29, 1966, August 18, 1966, September 6, 1966
January 2, 1967, October 1, 1967, June 6,1968, November 26, 1968, July 3, 1969, February 24, 1970, March 14, 1970, February 11, 1971, March 18, 1971, March 12, 1971
Kissinger, Henry, 1923-
March 13, 1959, February 13, 1961
Knox, Victor Alfred, 1899-
January 5, 1951, September 18, 1952, June 15, 1953, October 21, 1959
Lausche, Frank John, 1895-
March 20, 1964
Lawrence, David, 1888-
September 6, 1966
Long, Russell B.
July 17, 1956, August 22, 1963, June 21, 1967
Luce, Clare Boothe, 1903-1987.
February 19, 1946
Lunsford, Frank J.
January 13, 1950, January 9, 1950, April 16, 1951
McAllister, Thomas Francis, 1896-
September 20, 1962
McCarthy, Eugene J., 1916-
November 6, 1967, July 8, 1968
McGee, Gale W. (Gale William), 1915-
March 4, 1972
McGovern, George S. (George Stanley), 1922-
October 28, 1968, July 14, 1972
McGrath, Tom J.
May 19, 1947, August 15, 1947
Machrowicz, Thaddeus Michael, 1899-
April 24, 1959, October 20, 1959
MacLachlan, James Angell, 1891-
October 10, 1958, November 26, 1958, February 20, 1959
MacLeish, Archibald, 1892-
June 26, 1960
Macmillan, Harold, 1894-
July 8, 1968
McNamara, Patrick Vincent, 1894-1966.
May 9, 1955, May 21, 1959, November 6, 1960, December 22, 1960, July 17, 1961
Marc, Alexandre.
May 25, 1962, July 12, 1962, October 24, 1962
Marshall, Charles Burton, 1908-
February 27, 1960
Martin, Paul, 1903-
October 17, 1945, August 19, 1960, June 24, 1963, July 12, 1963, July 20, 1965, October 1, 1968, November 22, 1968, October 29, 1970
Mason, Philip P. (Philip Parker), 1927-
May 15, 1963
Meader, George, 1907-
May 3, 1951
Meagher, John Patrick, 1922-
May 23, 1956, May 14, 1956, June 29, 1956
Merchant, Livingston Tallmadge, 1903-
June 6, 1968, June 12, 1968, October 3, 1969
Michener, Daniel Roland, 1900-
October 13, 1961
Milliken, Helen W. (Helen Wallbank)
August 10, 1972
Milliken, William G., 1922-
June 12, 1972, June 19, 1972
Mills, Wilbur Daigh, 1909-
April 1, 1958
Mondale, Walter F., 1928-
February 24,1971
Moody, Blair, 1902-1954
May 15, 1951, September 24, 1951
Moore, Arthur J. (Arthur James), 1888-1974.
May 10, 1955
Moore, Walden.
July 14, 1950, August 22, 1950, September 21, 1950, May 9, 1951, August 22, 1951, September 11, 1951, November 30, 1951, April 4, 1952, January 18, 1956, January 5, 1956
January 3, 1956, February 15, 1956, September 25, 1956, April 29, 1957, August 2, 1957, December 16, 1957, 1958, February 2, 1960, March 2, 1960, May 19, 1960, May 10, 1960, August 2, 1960, October 31, 1960, 1961, February 28, 1962, May 22, 1962, May 21, 1962, May 28, 1962
March 15, 1963, October 15, 1963, December 10, 1963, December 12, 1963, March 12, 1964, April 21, 1964, April 9, 1964, March 10, 1967, December 23, 1969, May 12, 1970, August 8, 1972
Morgan, Thomas Ellsworth, 1906-
April 22, 1959, August 9, 1960, March 28, 1961, March 30, 1970, April 22, 1971
Morrison, William Angus, 1914-
April 20, 1960
Morse, Wayne Lyman, 1900-
June 6, 1955, March 17, 1958
Morton, Rogers C., 1914-
November 12, 1968, December 29, 1969
Murphy, Frank, 1890-1949.
November 19, 1945, January 3, 1946, February 8, 1946, April 1, 1949
Murrow, Edward R.
May 20, 1959
Muskie, Edmund S., 1914-
July 9, 1968
Nicholson, Patrick.
March 11, 1958, April 19, 1958, April 23, 1958, June 11, 1958, July 7,1958, June 16, 1961, October 1961, November 14, 1961, December 1961, February 8, 1962, June 15, 1962, March 25, 1963, June 25, 1963, April 1964, September 5, 1964
Nicholson, Robert Lawrence, 1908-
February 20, 1960, March 31, 1960, June 4, 1960, October 22, 1960, March 1961, May 1, 1961, June 1961, August 5, 1961, February 4, 1962, March 1962, April 1964, September 5, 1964
Niehuss, Marvin Lemmon, 1903-
September 22, 1949
Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-
April 9, 1951, January 14, 1969, November 30, 1960, September 1960, December 29, 1960, October 7, 1960, June 20, 1966, March 30, 1967
Norstad, Lauris, 1907-
July 12, 1963, December 11, 1963, December 31, 1963, January 8, 1964, July 14, 1966, August 16, 1966
North, Roy Moses, 1889-
August 15, 1957, September 3, 1957
O'Hara, James G., 1925-
July 6, 1972
Oppenheimer, William Henry, 1883-
May 19, 1964, June 3, 1964, October 7, 1968, December 23, 1970, March 17, 1971, April 23, 1971
Osborne, Lithgow, 1892-
October 14, 1957, November 4, 1957, June 23, 1958, June 21, 1959, September 8, 1959, May 1960, June 2, 1960, August 1960, April 6, 1961, October 15, 1969
Parsons, Geoffrey, 1908-
November 16, 1955, November 19, 1955
Pearson, Lester B.
October 21, 1958, November 13, 1958, March 16, 1959, April 7, 1959, April, 1959, January 25, 1960, March 14, 1960, April 8, 1960, June 10, 1961, October 26, 1961, January 18, 1962, May 6, 1963, August 21, 1968, August 9, 1968, August 25, 1970
Percy, Charles H., 1919-
March 13, 1967
Peterson, Elly, 1914-
April 14, 1965, April 29, 1965, October 27, 1969
Paeetrequin, Odette.
March 1958, May 9, 1958, April 22, 1959, December 21, 1960, September 23, 1960, March 2, 1962, April 28, 1962, June 6, 1962, September 8, 1962, March 28, 1963, June 15, 1963, June 12, 1964, September 2, 1964, January 9, 1966, November 3, 1966
Pilcher, John Leonard, 1898-
July 10, 1957, February 18, 1961, March 11, 1961, May 9, 1961, June 14, 1961, March 27, 1962
Plant, Marcus L., 1911-
May 1,1961
Potter, Charles E. (Charles Edward), 1916-1979.
August 20, 1949, September 7, 1949, June 19, 1953
Priest, J Percy.
August 11, 1950, August 9, 1950
Quimby, Thomas H. E. (Thomas Howard Emerson), 1918-
January 14, 1959, February 1959, March 11, 1959, May 29, 1959, July 23, 1959
Rabaut, Louis Charles, 1886-1961.
October 19, 1959
Rice, Warner Grenelle, 1899-
March 30, 1951, July 28, 1951, August 21, 1952, March 31, 1953, June 18, 1953, September 20, 1954, March 19, 1954, December 24, 1954, July 30, 1959, September 4, 1959, January 24, 1961, February 9, 1961, April 24, 1961, March 10, 1961
March 12, 1962, April 3, 1962, October 18, 1963, March 29, 1965, August 10, 1967, October 9, 1967, October 26, 1967, March 18, 1970, August 18, 1970
Richards, James Prioleau, 1894-
August 2, 1952, May 5, 1955, September 2, 1955
Riegle, Donald Wayne, 1938-
June 18, 1969
Roberts, Owen J. (Owen Josephus), 1875-1955.
May 10, 1950, July 10, 1950, September 5, 1950, October 24, 1950, April 19, 1951, May 8, 1951, May 1, 1951, May 16, 1951, June 2, 1952, May 12, 1952, May 20, 1953
Robertson, Wishart McLea,1891-
October 31, 1960, June 19, 1961, November 7, 1963
Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich), 1908-
October 19, 1959, July 8, 1960, August 25, 1960, March 13, 1961, February 26, 1962, September 21, 1962, July 17, 1963, September 18, 1963, October 16, 1963, October 29, 1963
January 27, 1964, February 18, 1964, March 27, 1964, January 19, 1965, January 4, 1965, January 15, 1965, January 17, 1966, August 11, 1967, April 2, 1968
Rockefeller, Winthrop, 1912-1973.
August 28, 1964, February 15, 1966, October 25, 1968
Roijan, J. H. van (Jan Herman)
May 13, 1959
Romney, George W., 1907-
November 10, 1959, January 12, 1962, January 18, 1963, April 12, 1963, May 4, 1964, July 29, 1964, October 15, 1964, November 13, 1964, December 1, 1964, May 3, 1965, May 25, 1966, May 10, 1966, August 8, 1966, November 3, 1966, March 11, 1960, March 14, 1968, February 4, 1969, May 23,1969
Romney, Lenore LaFount.
October 11, 1967, March 25, 1968
Roosevelt, James, 1907-
February 13, 1956
Ruppe, Philip E.
February 6, 1968, March 15, 1968, May 23, 1972
Rusk, Dean, 1909-
April 26, 1961
Russell, Bertrand, 1872-1970.
August 26, 1952, September 15, 1952, February 5, 1953, March 12, 1953
Russell, Richard B. (Richard Brevard), 1897-1971.
June 16, 1950, May 2, 1955
Ruthven, Alexander Grant, 1882-
November 26, 1945, September 30, 1949
Sewell, John.
October 26, 1966, April 18, 1967, August 3, 1967, September 26, 1967, November 1, 1967, November 20, 1967, March 17, 1969, January 19, 1970, May 13, 1971, May 30, 1972
Shawcross, Hartly, 1902-
July 16, 1959, September 10, 1959, September 30, 1959, December 14, 1959, June 19, 1961, February 20, 1962
Shotwell, James Thomson, 1874-1965.
April 14, 1960, May 31, 1960
Slosson, Preston W. (Preston William), 1892-
July 7, 1950
Smith, Allan Frederick, 1911-
December 11, 1962
Smith, Margaret Chase, 1897-
Ca. May, 1950, July 31, 1950, February 8, 1966
Spaak, Paul Henri, 1899-1972.
July 4, 1963
Sparkman, John, 1899-1985.
March 3, 1956, July 20, 1956, July 3, 1956, June 8, 1957, March 24, 1958
Spock, Benjamin, 1903-
June 2, 1971
Stanford, George Alonzo, 1917-
March 10, 1958
Stanley, Augustus Owsley, 1867-1958.
June 23, 1950
Stanton, Frank, 1908-
September 26, 1957
Stevenson, Adlai E. (Adlai Ewing), 1900-1965
April 3, 1961
Stevenson, Adlai E. (Adlai Ewing), 1930-
November 14, 1968
Strauss, Franz Josef, 1915-
November 24, 1961
Streit, Clarence Kirshman, 1896-
December 28, 1950, June 8, 1953, May 20, 1958, June 3, 1958, November 12, 1958, December 8, 1958, January 27, 1959, February 9, 1959, October 15, 1959, March 3, 1960, April 4, 1961, March 29, 1961, January 25, 1965, May 19, 1965, March 16, 1967, October 5, 1967, December 5, 1969, May 14, 1971
Sulzberger, C. L. (Cyrus Leo), 1912-
August 27, 1962, October 4, 1962
Swainson, John Burley, 1925-
November 1, 1961, January 2, 1962, January 30, 1962
Taft, Robert A. (Robert Alphonso), 1889-1953.
August 29, 1949, September 6, 1949
Talmadge, Herman E. (Herman Eugene), 1913-
January 28, 1950, January 21, 1950, January 6, 1950, January 6, 1961, August 6, 1957, December 28, 1957
Thomas, Elbert Duncan, 1883-1953.
June 16, 1950, July 11, 1950, August 29, 1950, September 11, 1950
Thomson, J. A.
January 3, 1961
Truman, Harry S., 1884-1972.
May 3, 1950
Tunney, James Joseph, 1897-
February 26, 1946
Tuttle, Elbert Parr, 1897-
April 20, 1965
Udall, Morris K.
November 5, 1968
Udall, Stewart L.
December 7, 1963
Urey, Harold Clayton, 1893-
September 17, 1951, September 16, 1971
Vandenberg, Arthur H. (Arthur Hendrick), 1884-1951.
November 26, 1945, May 13, 1950, May 25, 1950, October 24, 1950, April 5, 1951, July 25, 1952
Vander Jagt, Guy, 1931-
May 22, 1972
Vander Velde, Lewis G. (Lewis George), 1890-1975.
January 22, 1958, January 9, 1958, June 19, 1958, January 1960, February 12, 1960, March 1960, April 22, 1960, November 29, 1960, February 14, 1961, May 12, 1961, February 16, 1962
Wagner, Rudolph.
May 28, 1957, June 24, 1957, April 21, 1958, July 20, 1958, August 29, 1958, February 24, 1959, May 4, 1959, May 25, 1959, August 17, 1959, February 13, 1960, November 9, 1960, February 17, 1961, May 20, 1961, December 9, 1961
April 16, 1962, April 1963, May 22, 1963, June 7, 1963, November 11, 1963, August 22, 1966, December 17, 1966, August 21, 1967, October 4, 1968, April 16, 1969, August 25, 1969
Wallace, Richard J.
May 15, 1959, July 11, 1961, March 13, 1962, April 20, 1964, March 23, 1965, September 13, 1966, December 23, 1969, August 27, 1970, January 27, 1971, February 25, 1972
Walther, G. von.
January 12, 1962
Warner, Robert Mark, 1927-
June 29, 1957, July 31, 1957, November 18, 1957, December 20, 1957, June 24, 1958, August 28, 1958, February 16, 1959, September 15, 1959, October 22, 1959, November 16, 1959, December 2, 1959, December 18, 1959
January 14, 1960, April 27, 1960, August 10, 1960, January 17, 1961, February 1, 1961, May 10, 1962, October 16, 1962, May 1, 1963, March 31, 1965, September 2, 1966, January 4, 1967, August 4, 1967
September 19, 1968, December 16, 1968, June 18, 1969, September 15, 1969, May 22, 1970, May 27, 1970, July 6, 1970, March 9, 1971, April 22, 1971, May 28, 1971, August 27, 1971, March 7, 1972, April 18, 1972, May 12, 1972
Washburn, Abbott McConnell, 1915-
May 14, 1954, November 1,1957
Weltner, Charles Longstreet.
February 23, 1965, January 17, 1966
White, E. B. (Elwyn Brooks), 1899-
July 8, 1960
Wichers, W.C. (Willard C.)
July 21, 1953, August 1954, September 4, 1954 October 4, 1954, November 2, 1954, January 24, 1958, March 13, 1958, April 7, 1958, March 11, 1959, May 5, 1959, July 1959, October 8, 1959
January 15, 1960, February 11, 1960, September 7, 1960, February 15, 1962, March 8, 1962, June 28, 1962, November 2, 1966, March 25, 1969, April 16, 1971
Wilder, Thornton, 1897-1975.
October 20, 1961
Wilgress, Leolyn Dana, 1892-
October 16, 1957, December 20, 1957, September 22, 1958
Williams G. Mennen, 1911-
May 12, 1949, January 1950, June 22, 1950, August 1950, May 3, 1951, June 19, 1952, May 1953, November 1954, May 29, 1957, March 11, 1958, May 6, 1958, January 22, 1959, February 25, 1959, March 1959, April 23, 1959, July 1959, September 14, 1959, February 22, 1960, July 26, 1960, December 22, 1960, February 18, 1970, May 6, 1970
Williams, Harrison A.
February 28, 1956
Wolcott, Jesse Paine, 1893-1969.
February 7, 1951, September 26, 1951
Woodside, Willson.
March 10, 1961, July 7, 1961, September 14, 1961, February 24, 1964
Wyatt, Wilson W. (Wilson Watkins), 1905-
January 17, 1962
Young, Stephen M. (Stephen Marvin), 1889-1984.
February 2, 1960